Guide to the Washington State Federation of Teachers Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1937-2006; 2201-001; 20 cubic feet (20 boxes)
  - WASHINGTON STATE FEDERATION OF TEACHERS RECORDS, RECORD GROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-20/2)
    - SUBJECT FILES, 1943-2006; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 11/7-17/28)
      - TIAA/CREF changes, 1996 (Box-folder 16/37)
      - Training Committee, 1996 (Box-folder 16/38)
      - Tuition fee waiver bills, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 16/39)
      - Unemployment insurance, 2005 (Box-folder 16/40)
      - Unemployment Insurance Advisory Committee, 2004 (Box-folder 16/41)
      - Unemployment insurance claims, 1995 (Box-folder 16/42)
      - Unemployment insurance claims from members4, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 16/43)
      - Unemployment insurance issues and cases, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 16/44)
      - United Classified Workers Union of Washington election, 1999 (Box-folder 16/45)
      - United Faculty of Eastern due process, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 16/46)
      - United Faculty of Washington State, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 16/47)
      - University of Washington organizing, 2002 (Box-folder 16/48)
      - Vancouver, 1947 (Box-folder 16/49)
      - Vocational education, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 16/50)
      - Voucher plan, 1970 (Box-folder 16/51)
      - VTI Council surveys, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 16/52)
      - Wage freeze data, 1971 (Box-folder 16/53)
      - Washington Education Association, 1945-1965 (Box-folder 16/54)
      - Washington Public Employees Association affiliation, 1986 (Box-folder 16/55)
      - Washington Public Employees Association affiliation, 2002 (Box-folder 16/56)
      - Washington State Council of Public Employees, 1951 (Box-folder 16/57)
      - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 16/58)
      - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 16/59)
      - Washington State Labor Council education resolutions, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Washington State Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1945-1965 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Washington State Teachers Retirement System, 1972 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Washington State University clerical workers, 1991 (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Western Washington University, c. 1988 (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Women's rights, 1973 (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers -- Washington Education Association cooperation, 1995 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers -- Washington Education Association cooperation, 1996 (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers -- Washington Education Association cooperation, 1999 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers -- Washington Education Association relations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Classified Council, 1999 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers College and University Council, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Community College Council, 1995 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers - Committee on Political Education, 1972 (Box-folder 17/15)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Legislative Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 17/16)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Policies Handbook, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Retired Teachers Federation, 1971 (Box-folder 17/18)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Retirees chapter, 1996 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers strategic plan, 1996 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Voc-Ed Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 17/21)
      - World Trade Organization rally, 1999 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - Yakima, 1946 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - Yakima Community College District agreement, 1974 (Box-folder 17/24)
      - Yakima Valley College Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 1485 - part 1 of 3, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - Yakima Valley College Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 1485 - part 2 of 3, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 17/26)
      - Yakima Valley College Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 1485 - part 3 of 3, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 17/27)
      - Yakima Valley Community College classified employees, 1998 (Box-folder 17/28)
    - LEGAL RECORDS, 1965-2005; SERIES IX (Box-folder 17/29-18/40)
      - Bargaining and arbitration report, 1990 (Box-folder 17/29)
      - Evergreen clauses and duration of contracts, 1990 (Box-folder 17/30)
      - Last best offer, 1972 (Box-folder 17/31)
      - Legal assistance plan, 1997 (Box-folder 17/32)
      - Legal correspondence, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 17/33)
      - Legal correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 17/34)
      - Legal correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 17/35)
      - Legal correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 17/36)
      - Legal correspondence, Undated, 2005 (Box-folder 17/37)
      - Legal defense correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 17/38)
      - Legal defense correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 17/39)
      - Legal defense correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 17/40)
      - Legal defense requests, 1995 (Box-folder 17/41)
      - Legal defense requests, 1996 (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Legal defense requests, 1997 (Box-folder 17/43)
      - Legal documents, 1970 (Box-folder 17/44)
      - ELS Language Centers, 1976 (Box-folder 17/45)
      - Grays Harbor College, PERC case 12484-E-96-2086, 1996 (Box-folder 17/46)
      - Hostetler v. Peninsula College Board of Trustees, et al., 1980 (Box-folder 17/47)
      - Kobe decision, PERC cases 8046-U-89-1742, 8688-U-90-1895, 1991 (Box-folder 17/48)
      - Lake Washington Technical College, PERC case 14511-U-99-03609, 1999 (Box-folder 17/49)
      - Bassett, Donaldson & Hafer: Yakima Teachers case, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17/50)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: Bremerton non--renewal case, 1973 (Box-folder 17/51)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: Lasley letter, 1969 (Box-folder 17/52)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: Pangborne case, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 17/53)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: Port Orchard case, 1969 (Box-folder 17/54)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: South Kitsap case, 1972 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: Western Washington State College, 1974 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Smith, Welden, Kaplan and Young: Gaylord case, Tacoma # 461, 1973 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Edmonds School District, 1971 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Elma School District, Gillis case, 1970 (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Hoquiam High School: grooming regulations for students, 1970 (Box-folder 18/6)
      - Port Angeles Local # 793: Williams case, 1970 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Washington State Attorney General's opinion: duty-free lunch, 1966 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - Washington State Attorney General's opinion: professional negotiations, 1965 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Washington State Attorney General's opinion: transfer between districts, 1966 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers: H.B. 483, 1967 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Dolton case, Illinois: right to join organizaton, 1968 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Non-renewal brief: Green, 1972 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - MacDonald, Hoague and Bayless: agency shop brief, 1970 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Serrano v. Priest, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Truax case, 1971 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - 40-60 requirement court test, 1969 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Nixon Executive Order 11941: collective bargaining for federal employees, 1969 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Marian Pinichet v. Edmonds School District, 1965 (Box-folder 18/19)
      - PEMCO Insurance Company, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Schoch, et al. v. Montesano School District: student dress ruling, 1969 (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Teacher evaluation: RCW 28.67, 1969 (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Noe v. Edmonds School District, 1973 (Box-folder 18/23)
      - U.S. Supreme Court decisions: constitutional rights of teachers, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 18/24)
      - U.S. Supreme Court decisions: constitutional rights in public schools, 1969 (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Out-of-court settlement, Green River Community College, 1977 (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Shared Health Systems, Inc.: NLRB case 19-UC-250 transcript -- Part 1 of 3, 1980 (Box-folder 18/27)
      - Shared Health Systems, Inc.: NLRB case 19-UC-250 transcript -- Part 2 of 3, 1980 (Box-folder 18/28)
      - Shared Health Systems, Inc.: NLRB case 19-UC-250 transcript -- Part 3 of 3, 1980 (Box-folder 18/29)
      - Yakima Valley College: PERC case 811-E-77-149, 1977 (Box-folder 18/30)
      - Bates Voc-Tech instructors, 1977 (Box-folder 18/31)
      - Clover Park Voc-Tec: PERC case 883-8-77-171, 1977 (Box-folder 18/32)
      - Community College District No. 5: PERC case 1374-E-78-273, 1978 (Box-folder 18/33)
      - ITT Peterson School of Business19-RC-8986, 1978 (Box-folder 18/34)
      - Lake Washington School District: PERC case 896-E-77-175, 1978 (Box-folder 18/35)
      - Renton School District: PERC case 236-CEW-148, 1977 (Box-folder 18/36)
      - Renton School District: PERC case 941-E-77-187, 1979 (Box-folder 18/37)
      - Shoreline Community College arbitration 75-39-0088-78, 1978 (Box-folder 18/38)
      - Washington Educational Resource Associates, Inc.: NLRB case 19-RC-8250, 1980 (Box-folder 18/39)
      - Arbitration No. 75 39 0203 79, Scott matter, 1980 (Box-folder 18/40)
      - SPEECHES, 1964-1978; SERIES X (Box-folder 18/41-18/45)
      - Arthur D. Grafious speech "The A.F. of T." delivered to education classes, Eastern Washington University, 1968 (Box-folder 18/41)
      - Ross Rieder speeches, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 18/42)
      - Viet Nam Moratorium: script for Washington State Federation of Teachers statement, 1970 (Box-folder 18/43)
      - Statements to Joint Committee on Education of Washington State Legislature, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 18/44)
      - Speeches, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 18/45)
    - PUBLICATIONS AND EPHEMERA, SERIES XI
      - WASHINGTON STATE FEDERATION OF TEACHERS PUBLICATIONS, 1946-2003; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 18/46-19/9)
        - Brochure draft, 1972 (Box-folder 18/46)
        - Evergreen Educator, 1946 (Box-folder 18/47)
        - Washington State Teacher, 1958-1974 (Box-folder 18/48)
        - Federation Focus newsletter, 1968 (Box-folder 18/49)
        - Union Teacher newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/50)
        - Union Teacher newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 18/51)
        - The Spotlight, 1987-2000 (Box-folder 18/52)
        - School News from Olympia, 1947 (Box-folder 18/53)
        - Olympia Bulletin, 1973 (Box-folder 18/54)
        - Legisletter, 1983 (Box-folder 18/55)
        - Legisletter, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 18/56)
        - Legisletter, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 18/57)
        - Legisletter, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 18/58)
        - Legisletter, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18/59)
        - Legisletter, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 18/60)
        - Legisletter, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 18/61)
        - Legisletter, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 18/62)
        - Legisletter, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 18/63)
        - Legisletter, 2000 (Box-folder 18/64)
        - College and University Outlook, 1978 (Box-folder 19/1)
        - Perspective: 4-year College and University Council newsletter, 1989 (Box-folder 19/2)
        - Classified Council newsletter, Undated (Box-folder 19/3)
        - Perspective: Community College Council newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/4)
        - Perspective: K-12 Council newsletter, 1989 (Box-folder 19/5)
        - Perspective: Vocational-Technical Institutes Council newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/6)
        - Washington State Federation of Teachers Women Speak Out, 1973 (Box-folder 19/7)
        - Wake Up Call newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 19/8)
        - Washington Federation of Teachers flyers and handouts, 2003 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - NEWSLETTERS AND CIRCULARS OF WASHINGTON STATE FEDERATIONS OF TEACHERS AFFILIATES AND OTHER UNIONS, 1934-1989; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 19/10-19/35)
      - Everett Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 772 newsletters and circulars, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/10)
      - The Federation Paper, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 19/11)
      - The Federation Paper, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19/12)
      - Renton Federation of Teachers, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 19/13)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1971 (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1973 (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1974 (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1989 (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1971 (Box-folder 19/19)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box-folder 19/20)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/21)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box-folder 19/22)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Seattle Teacher, 1949 (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Seattle Teachers' League, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 19/25)
      - Seattle Teachers Association, 1965 (Box-folder 19/26)
      - Tacoma Federation of Teachers, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 19/27)
      - United Classified Workers Union, 1991 (Box-folder 19/28)
      - Washington State affiliates of Washington State Federation of Teachers, 1945-1965 (Box-folder 19/29)
      - Washington State affiliates of Washington State Federation of Teachers (part 1 of 2), 1965-1972 (Box-folder 19/30)
      - Washington State affiliates of Washington State Federation of Teachers (part 2 of 2), 1965-1972 (Box-folder 19/31)
      - Washington State affiliates of Washington State Federation of Teachers, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 19/32)
      - Teacher organizations in other states, 1947-1976 (Box-folder 19/33)
      - Teacher organizations in other states, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 19/34)
      - Other labor organizations, 1945-1965 (Box-folder 19/35)
      - REPORTS, 1957-1965; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 19/36-19/39)
      - Seattle Public Schools, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 19/36)
      - Seattle Public Schools Citizens' Advisory Committees, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 19/37)
      - Seattle Citizens Committee for School Support, 1964 (Box-folder 19/38)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers reports, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 19/39)
    - EPHEMERA, 1965-1979; SUBSERIES IV (Box-folder 19/40-20/2)
      - Ephemera (part 1 of 2), 1965-1971 (Box-folder 19/40)
      - Ephemera (part 2 of 2), 1965-1971 (Box-folder 19/41)
      - Ephemera (part 1 of 2), 1966-1979 (Box-folder 20/1)
      - Ephemera (part 2 of 2), 1966-1979 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - BREMERTON FEDERATION OF TEACHERS, AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 336, RECORD GROUP 2 (Box-folder 20/3-20/20)
    - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, 1935-1960; SERIES I (Box-folder 20/3-20/9)
      - Constitution and bylaws, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 20/3)
      - History of Local 336, Undated, 1951 (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Executive Board minutes, Undated, 1950-1960 (Box-folder 20/5)
      - General meetings, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Membership lists, 1935-c. 1960 (Box-folder 20/7)
      - Administrative records and notes, Undated (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Circulars to members and teachers, Undated, 1950 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES, 1934-1965; SERIES II (Box-folder 20/10-20/20)
      - General correspondence, 1934-1953 (Box-folder 20/10)
      - American Federation of Teachers - National Education Association issues, Undated, 1963 (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Agreements and negotiations, 1937-1965 (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Bremerton School District, 1942-1959 (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Bremerton Central Trades and Labor Council, 1937-1946 (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Bremerton strike: press clippings, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Matson hearing, 1954 (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Newsletters, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 20/17)
      - Representation election, 1964 (Box-folder 20/18)
      - Research Committee, Undated (Box-folder 20/19)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers, 1937 (Box-folder 20/20)
  - LAKE WASHINGTON FEDERATION OF TEACHERS, AMERCAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 2298, 1970-1973; RECORD GROUP 3 (Box-folder 20/21-21/22)
    - Records of American Federation of Teachers Local 2298, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Course materials for Ed 445a, Professional Negotiations, 1973 (Box-folder 20/22)
  - SEATTLE FEDERATION OF TEACHERS, AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 200, RECORD GROUP 4 (Box-folder 20/23-20/36)
    - MINUTES, 1970-1971; SERIES I (Box-folder 20/23-20/24)
      - General membership meeting minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20/23)
      - Executive Board minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20/24)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1969-1972; SERIES II
      - Reports and records, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 20/25)
    - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES, 1951-1967; SERIES III (Box-folder 20/26-20/34)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 20/26)
      - Salary and policy issues, 1951-1959 (Box-folder 20/27)
      - Salary and policy reports, 1960 (Box-folder 20/28)
      - Salary and policy reports, 1961 (Box-folder 20/29)
      - Professional improvement program, 1962 (Box-folder 20/30)
      - Salary schedule and policy issues, 1963 (Box-folder 20/31)
      - Salary schedule and policy reports, 1964 (Box-folder 20/32)
      - Salary and policy reports, 1965 (Box-folder 20/33)
      - Salary and policy reports, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20/34)
    - NEWSLETTERS, 1960-1972; SERIES IV (Box-folder 20/35-20/36)
      - Newsletters, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 20/35)
      - Newsletters, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 20/36)
  - SEATTLE COMMUNITY COLLEGE FEDERATON OF TEACHERS, AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS LOCAL 1789, RECORD GROUP 5 (Box-folder 20/37-20/48)
    - SUBJECT FILES, 1971-1973; SERIES I (Box-folder 20/37-20/42)
      - Administrative bed check, 1971 (Box-folder 20/37)
      - Association for Higher Education propaganda, 1972 (Box-folder 20/38)
      - SCCD budget and organizing, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/39)
      - SCCFT Faculty Voice, 1972 (Box-folder 20/40)
      - SCCFT newsletter copy, 1971 (Box-folder 20/41)
      - Seattle Community College strike: photographs, 1972 (Box-folder 20/42)
    - GRIEVANCE RECORDS, 1970-1973; SERIES II (Box-folder 20/43-20/48)
      - Galvin matter, 1973 (Box-folder 20/43)
      - Jacobsen petition, 1973 (Box-folder 20/44)
      - Pinegar matter, Undated (Box-folder 20/45)
      - Marilyn Smith matter, 1971 (Box-folder 20/46)
      - Bob Tighe matter, 1971 (Box-folder 20/47)
      - Grievances, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 20/48)
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1962-1972; 2201-002; 2 cubic feet (2 boxes)
  Correspondence, minutes, financial records, reports, ephemera.
  Donated by Ross Rieder, 9/5/1973.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, circa 1968-1972; 2201-003; 1.39 cubic feet (3 boxes)
  Correspondence, reports, case files, ephemera.
  Donated by the Federation, 3/9/1976.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1952-1980; 1974-1979; 2201-004; 10 cubic feet (10 boxes)
  Organizational material, correspondence, minutes, financial records, conferences and conventions, legal documents, clippings, "Daily Productions", subject series.
  "Daily Productions" include outgoing letters, minutes, agendas, and other material, arranged chronologically.
  Donated by the Federation, 8/27/1981.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1969-1978; 1976-1978; 2201-005; .44 cubic feet
  Minutes, 1976-1979; correspondence, reports, contracts, press releases, newsletter, conferences and conventions, 1969-1972.
  Bulk of the accession is minutes of the Executive Board, 1976-1978.
  Donated by the Federation, 5/8/1984.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1950-1978; 2201-006; .56 cubic feet
  Correspondence, press releases, newsletters, conferences and conventions, clippings, ephemera.
  1969 correspondence of Ross K. Rieder, Washington State Federation of Teachers president. Bulk of accession is records of four local union: Teachers, American Federation of (AFL). Local 200, Seattle.; (AFL). Local 1789, Seattle Community College.; AFL. Local 1485, Yakima Valley College.; AFL. Local 772, Everett.
  Donated by the Federation, 10/22/1984.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1970-1985; 2201-007; 1 cubic foot (1 box)
  Executive Board minutes 1970-1972, 1979: correspondence, reports, daily productions, conferences and conventons, 1972-1985.
  Donated by the Federation, 9/1/1987.
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1947-2006; 1977-2006; 2201-008; 5 cubic feet 5 boxes
  Arranged as received.
  Newsletters, conference proceedings, minutes, project files, legal materials, planning files, local branch records, subject files, and other materials.
  Washington State Federation of Teachers, February and May 2009
  - AFT/Seattle "Professional" (Box-folder 1)
  - Agency Shop (Box-folder 1)
  - Classified Project (Box-folder 1)
  - CBA's (Box-folder 1)
  - CC/TC Conference, Jan. 1993 (Box-folder 1)
  - Convention, 2000 (Box-folder 1)
  - Convention Resolutions, 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Convention Resolutions, 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Convention, 1997 (Box-folder 1)
  - Edmonds CC Kobe Decision (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT Convention, 1996 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, June 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, July 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, May 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, April 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, March 99 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Feb. 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Jan. 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT Ex Bd Minutes, 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, July 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, April-June 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Jan-March 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Feb. 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Jan. 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Nov/Dec1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Oct. 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd, Sept. 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1998 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1997 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1996 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1995 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1994 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ex Bd Minutes, 1993 (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT Keep: (Box-folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1978 (Box-folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1977 (Box-folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining Leg. Hist., To 1980 (Box-folder 1)
  - Equity Campaign, 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Higher Ed. Conference, 1999 (Box-folder 1)
  - Higer Ed. Conference, 1997 (Box-folder 1)
  - Edmonds Case File (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT Literature (Box-folder 1)
  - Hudson Background (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT Policies Handbook (Box-folder 1)
  - K-12 Council (Box-folder 1)
  - K-12 Council Minutes (Box-folder 1)
  - Legal Decisions (Box-folder 1)
  - WFT/AFT-WSU Agreement (Box-folder 2)
  - DOC Education Program (Box-folder 2)
  - WFT Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box-folder 2)
  - WFT Task Force on Statewide Bargaining Issues (Box-folder 2)
  - WFT/WEA (Box-folder 2)
  - WPEA (Box-folder 2)
  - WPEA Affiliation Info, 1986 (Box-folder 2)
  - WSU Clerical (Box-folder 2)
  - Yakima Class ORG, 1998 (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Defense Requests, 1997 (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Defense Request, 1996 (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Defense Request, 1995 (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Defense: Copies of correspondence (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Assistance Plan (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Assistance Plan, 1997 (Box-folder 2)
  - Misc. Legal Defense, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Opinion: Evergreen Clause (Box-folder 2)
  - Legal Candidates, 1996 (Box-folder 2)